Then we are going to do the outer layer of the puller sound effect, select the inner layer of the clothing panel, copy and paste one layer, move them to the inner layer near the 3D window.
The reason why we don't use the column layer here is that the column layer will automatically exist.
After that, we need to delete these lines, activate the outer layer panel, move them to the inner layer, try to avoid overlapping.
Then use the line powder tool to mix the upper and lower layers of the clothing inside and outside layers together.
The sleeves are also mixed together.
The back is also operated in the same way.
Then remove the needle and use the free powder tool.
Press the same müssen Adhere sleeve and outer layer panels.
Select the free powder tool, First create a seam line part of the shoulder wet, press SHIFT to re-match the front and back of the phone in the same direction of volume.
Loosen the SHIFT key to complete the creation.
Open the simulation to examine the穿着性.
After the穿着性, activate all of the lining panels.
Explain to maintain overall stability .
Then the waistband is simulated
You can see that there are two folds in the front
This is because the rope is deleted
But the sewing line between the ropes is not deleted
Use the editor sewing line tool to delete them
Check the chest at this time
Will find that the board is bent
This is because the type of sewing line is Custom Angle
The seam will bulge at the edge
After changing to Turned, the seam will be flat
The rest of the folding position is also modified
For example, the hem and the back of the upper eye
If the chest is not smooth at the time
You can modify the position of the seam line according to the method in the previous video
Then select the inner layer of the board to freeze them
Then select the outer layer of these boards
Give them the fabric of the sleeves and skirt
After changing the fabric, the board produced some folds
Select the front and middle lines
In the process of moving them
Press the Shift key to move them to the level
The advantage of this stretching is
There will be folds
At the same time, the sleeves will not be affected
The point that alone drags the upper eye
Can increase the folds of the chest
Lower the outer layer of the chest
To see the more detailed fold effect
Press the Shift key to move them to the level
Activate the inner layer of the board and modify it together
Press the Ctrl key to move them to the level
Shorten the line in the front
After shortening, the bulge in the front part will be flattened
Then you can merge the front and the back
If you want to do this, press Ctrl C to move the edges
After merging, if you want to add a part of the fold
You can choose the side line to keep it unchanged
Then drag them to the level
At this time, the version may have holes in the 3D window
If there are penetrations, remember to deal with unstable places at any time.
Do the same for the back and center.
If the drag is not very effective, then pause the simulation.
Pull out the sheet first, then simulate.
Combine the back piece.
Reduce the particle strength.
You can manually drag the sheet to adjust the distribution of the fold.
Then reduce the particle strength to 5 and adjust the sheet repeatedly.
Reduce the particle strength to 5 and adjust the sheet repeatedly.
There are fewer folds at the seam area.
We can increase the fold by modifying the physical properties of the fabric.
Reduce the particle strength to 0 by copying the existing fabric.
The particle strength refers to the transformation of the fabric.
The number is zero, the fabric is not easy to deform, so the original wrinkles will appear all over the seam.
After adjustment, turn on the transparency display.
You will find that there is more volume on the waist, you can adjust it through the rules.
The shrink rate is set to negative, which can shrink the part of the grid.
On the panel, click and drag the mouse.
As the blue area is deepened, the fabric will be shrunk after simulation.
The back piece is also operated in the same way.
The corner on the side of the back piece is too sharp.
After sewing, there will be a protrusion, slightly adjust it according to the rhythm.
After simulation, you can see that the waist does not appear.
It is more suitable for models.
Now let's make the pattern of the outer circle of the costume.
First select the line of the inner layer of the costume and the sleeve part.
Check the total length.
Then select the rectangular tool.
Create a rectangular with twice the width and a height of 15 mm.
Create a rectangular pattern.
Use the line powder tool.
First click on the edge of the flower, then press the Shift key.
In the same direction, click on the front, sleeve and back pieces.
Then select these two flower edges.
In the menu in the right-hand corner, select the side of the addition.
The side of the flower will be arranged on the side of the top and sleeve.
Cool the back piece to prevent it from being unstable.
Activate simulation.
The flower side of the pattern is relatively large.
It will still turn out automatically.
If it doesn't turn out, you can drag it out.
After stabilizing, put the sides together.
If it's too sharp, control the screen and adjust the straightening point of the Oscillator.
After stabilizing, adjust the diagonal of the edge of the flower to 8 mm.
Shortening of the apologize dimension is decreased to 1 mm.
ראל
Press it on the virtual model because of the pressure of the negative value applied to the edge of the flower.
Then select all the panels, activate them, untangle them, and simulate them together to ensure stability.